# **Alexandra Llamas**

### **SUMMARY**

Motivated software developer with proficiencies in front end development, back end development, and automation

Offers 2 years of experience in software oriented professional roles

Looking to secure a job in a reputable company that will utilize my skills and further enhance my knowledge in front end or back end programming

## Portland, OR 97229 (971) 724 - 9481 alexandracllamas@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, React, Python, C++, Node.js UI design and implementation Agile development

Team player

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Multnomah County**, Portland — Front End Developer Intern

JANUARY 2020 - JUNE 2020

Collaborated with a team of interns to build a new Multnomah County MVC web app from the ground up

Single handedly led, designed, and developed an appealing and responsive user interface for the app

# **Jama Software**, Portland — Front End Developer Intern

JANUARY 2020 - JUNE 2020

Modified existing software interfaces to add new features and provide a user friendly environment

Worked closely with team members to identify and fix front end bugs

## **Act-On Software**, Portland — Automation Intern

JULY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

Resolved lengthy process of SSL web certificate generation by automating creative technical solutions

Constructed requirements, scope, and sequence of automation by collaborating with cross functional teams

# **XPO Logistics**, Portland — Back End Developer Intern

JANUARY 2019 - JUNE 2019

Utilized the RAD framework to build over 20 APIs for XPO Logistics mobile apps

Applied test driven development to assess APIs prior to being developed, built, and released

### **EDUCATION**

### **B.S. in Computer Science**

Portland State University Graduated June 2020

Cum Laude Honors Standing 3.74/4.00 GPA

Coursework in Front End Web Development, Full Stack Development, Data Structures, Programming Systems, Databases, Open Source Software, and Web Security

Intel Andy Grove Scholarship Recipient

Red Cross Leaders Save Lives Scholarship Recipient

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

### Personal Website

https://alexandralla.github.io/

### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandra-llamas-38825319a

### Github

@alexandralla